[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday", "Sunday"], "TIME": ["afternoon", "morning"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "When did you hear about what had happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Carl was killed Friday afternoon and I didn't hear about it until Sunday morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "-- that this may happen one day?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "I was always concerned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tim 11"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "He was a very gentle, very caring son, and I was very close to him, and his passion was doing this research, his passion for many years was the weather phenomenon, and he started chasing with Tim 11 years ago and he loved it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Is that what you're hearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Sal, how would you like Carl to be remembered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "First and foremost, as our son, and beyond that, we would like to thank everyone in Oklahoma and all the news media.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carl"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "And, Ben, even though the loss of life at the moment hasn't quite reached the levels of the previous Oklahoma tornado 10 days ago, in terms of power it wasn't quite as powerful but clearly from what people are telling me, including yourself that night, it was a pretty awesome tornado, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Yes, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"], "LOCATION": ["Oklahoma"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Yes, it's a tough thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tim"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Have you guys talked about this as potentially a reason not to continue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "In terms of the safety of it, I mean, especially when you have somebody as well respected and as safe as Tim was, it leads you to believe that it doesn't take a moment of recklessness or stupidity to get yourself in a situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent", "10 percent", "80 percent"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "CD", "NN", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "''", "NN", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What do they bring scientifically, if you like, to the way that we combat tornadoes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, let me tell you, there's a 10 percent scientific community, there's a 10 percent meteorology community and an 80 percent \"I want to go out and see something, get my adrenaline rush\" community that have no idea where the storm is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "How serious is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, it is still serious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Eastern Plains"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Mike Nelson, coming back to you, tell me about what's happening in Colorado in relation to the fires?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Well, today we had 100 degree temperatures on the Eastern Plains.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Nelson"], "LOCATION": ["Colorado"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Jesse, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I'm doing good, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, again, the assault on our Bill of Rights is just astounding that we're allowing the government to destroy all the protections in our country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What is the difference -- what is the difference between the police taking a DNA sample and fingerprinting you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Is he a victim of an attack on his own freedom of speech rights, the way that he's being treated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Why wouldn't you encourage people to do it that way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, maybe so, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Where do you draw the line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Do you agree with the Department of Justice and Eric Holder, the attorney general, targeting journalists, you know, going after the Associated Press or the FOX News journalists for information about potential leaks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think that we -- we got bigger fish to fry.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Department of Justice", "Associated Press"], "PERSON": ["Eric Holder"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "No, I'm saying if you take that position, though, if anybody takes that position, that he shouldn't be prosecuted for what he did, how could you then justify the targeting of journalists who are revealing equally valuable information in the public interest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "I fully agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Jesse, I mean, are you seriously thinking still about potentially running?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, 2016 would be the year to do it, Piers, because you don't -- as an independent, you don't want an incumbent, so the office will be wide open.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS"]}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What did you think of the IRS targeting right-wing groups?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, first of all, let me state one thing I would do is abolish the income tax and go to a national sales tax, and then you wouldn't even have the IRS, or you would reverse their role and you would make them the watchdog of the government to make sure they spend our money properly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Why have you continued it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, because it's always been about clearing my name and getting back my reputation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "But do you not feel slightly uncomfortable about the fact you're now suing his widow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "ENTURA: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Why was he near these bees to start with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "He was shredding a field for the lady.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "So he was removing I think some brush piles for his neighbor, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Do you know what agitated these bees because there were 40,000 of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "I'm sure the vibration of the tractor and the shredder.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "And what was the first that you know something awful was happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "JJ", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Me and my sister were leaving to take our kids to a park and my sister had to pull her car over and she went over to the tractor because he went on the tractor and I seen an ambulance and I was wondering why the ambulance was coming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Do they believe it was the combined effect of the stings themselves that killed your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "And were you yourself stung?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Yes, it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Were you yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Is he right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "AMM: Well, he may be right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Can you be vaccinated like you would anything else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Well, this is very -- that's why this is so critically important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "So we should applaud Michael Douglas for raising it even if he now wishes he hadn't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Douglas"]}}]